apr.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Statement | Alain Pinel Realtors

  * Properties
  * Agents/Offices
  * Communities
  * Services
  * Careers
  * About Us
  * ##### **TOOL** box ▼

  1. **Privacy**

We do not share with others any information we collect from you on this Site except to provide information or services that you have requested or with your permission.

    * Our Site contains links to third-party web sites. You will be subject to that site's privacy statement. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those other web sites.
    * Third party vendors we engage to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting, web-site development, and support, have access to your information, but they have agreed not to disclose the information or to use it for any purpose other than providing the requested services.
    * It may be necessary for us to disclose and use your information to enforce this Privacy Statement or any part of our General Terms and Conditions to protect our property or rights; to protect the safety of anyone; to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or improper activities, or for reasons we determine in good faith are necessary.
  2. **Security**

Our hosting services maintain its systems in accordance with industry standards to secure the information of its visitors. As you know information transmission over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be secure. You use the Site at your own risk.

  3. **California Residents**

California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship (1) a list of categories of personal information such as name, address, email address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties.

To request the above information please contact us by writing to customer service at:

  4. **Our Use of Information**

We use the information we collect on the Site (A) to provide you with the services that you ask to receive through the Site, including saving searches and, if you request it, sending you updates about those searches, (B) to receive periodic updates, (C) to answer your questions or complaints and (D) to refer you to sales associates.

  5. **Rights To Disclose**

We reserve the right to disclose any information to satisfy any third party, demand, and/or any subpoena, law, regulation, ordinance or government request if we determine, in our sole discretion, that we are required to respond to, or if it would be in our best interests to, respond to any such request, demand or subpoena.

  6. **Acceptance of Privacy Statement**

BY USING THE SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT, YOU CANNOT USE THE SITE. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time by posting a notice on the Site’s home page. Your use of the Site after the date of the last modification indicates to us that you agree to the changes.
